CV DIITDA



# Dede Saputra (Putra)

ACCOUNTANTS AND FINANCE, TAX SERVICES, STUDENT OF ESA UNGGUL UNIVERSITY

Hire Me

Download CV



file:///D:/My Porto/index.html 1/10

CV PUTRA

### About

I am a student at Esa Unggul University majoring in Business Accounting.

Besides that, I have worked at PT Sumber Griya Sejahtera for four years. I also have experience handling several clients in the property, accounting, finance, and marketing sectors.

### Basic Information

EMAIL:

dede.saputra@ptsgs.net

PHONE:

+62 813-7005-1699

ADDRESS:

Apartemen Green Park View, West Jakarta, Indonesia

LANGUAGE:

Bahasa Indonesia, English

Professional Skills

file:///D:/My Porto/index.html 2/10

#### CV PLITRA

ACCOUNTING	90%
ACCURACY	95%
MARKETING	85%

# Portfolio



file:///D:/My Porto/index.html 3/10

#### CV PUTRA







CV PLITRA



Work Experience

file:///D:/My Porto/index.html 5/10

CV PUTRA

DCT 2016 - OCT 2017

#### RETAIL

# Supervisor

I worked in a retail company at PT Tas Center Cemerlang as a Supervisor for one year.

NOV 2017 - NOV 2018

RETAIL

# Sales Executive

I work at the retail company PT Kawan Lama Group as a Sales Executive.

file:///D:/My Porto/index.html 6/10

CV PLITRA

NOV 2018 - UNTIL NOW

#### SERVICES

# Accountants and Finance

I work at the service company PT Sumber Griya Sejahtera. I am an accountant and finance.

# Education

file:///D:/My Porto/index.html 7/10

CV PUTRA

2008 - 2011

### Junior High School

# Public Junior High School

SMPN 14

My junior high school is at SMPN 14 Tangerang, I graduated 2011.

2011 - 2014

Senior High School

# Senior High School

SMK PUSTEK

My high school is at Pustek Serpong, I graduated in 2014.

file:///D:/My Porto/index.html

CV DIITDA

2020 - 2024

### Bachelor Degree

# **Business Accounting**

ESA UNGGUL UNIVERSITY

I am still studying for a bachelor's degree, academic year 2020 at Esa Unggul University.

### References



Hafiz STORE MANAGER

I work in a retail company, but I often use his services to be on the company's external audit team. For me he is a very professional and pleasant person. I hope we will always cooperate well in the future. Outside of work we always hangout or just talk.

file:///D:/My Porto/index.html 9/10

CV PUTRA



Dede Saputra(Putra)

© Creative CV. All rights reserved. Design - TemplateFlip

file:///D:/My Porto/index.html